showScene(true,topDown) next
Azumi "What if we are on the ground floor and not near the exit?" 1
Fury "Stay under the table and stay away from glass objects and hanging objects." 2
Azumi "We must be vigilant, afraid of aftershocks if the earthquake is strong. What caused the earthquake just now, huh?" 1
Fury "Hmm ... the earthquake is due to the shifting of the plates, not because of volcanic activity because this area is far from the volcano. 皆が集まる前にシャワー浴びてよ。10分以上はだめだよ。いい？" 2
Azumi "I am not sure..." exit(Azumi) 1
Fury "電話だ…ママからだ… こっちでは地震があったよ。そっちでも揺れを感じた？" enter(Ibu) setFace(Ibu,anxious) setPosition(Ibu,0.8) 2
Ibu as [mom_jpn] "うん、こちらでも揺れたよ。あなたたちは安全だよね。" 1
Fury "私たちは怖かったけど、今は大丈夫だよ。The earthquake is strong, Mom. I'm dizzy until I can't stand up." 2
Ibu as [mom_jpn] "Yes, the shake is fast. Mom also received a tsunami warning notification but was canceled. ふう、神様ありがとう。 [setFace(Ibu,happy)] あなたたちは何時にアニエールに着いたの？" setFace(Fury,1_happy) 1
Fury "16時ごろ、ママ。" 2
Ibu as [mom_jpn] "そしてアクティビティが始まるのは何時...？" 1
Fury "5時に始まるよ。ところで、タマおじさんの具合はどう？" 2
Ibu as [mom_jpn] "彼は今はだいぶいいよ。ただよく休まないとね。準備したほうがいいよ。もう4時45分だからね。もし何かあったら、電話して。じゃ、電話切るね。バイバイ。" 1
Fury "バイバイ、ママ。" exit(Ibu) 2
enter(Azumi) setPosition(Azumi,0.8) next
Azumi "誰から？" 1
Fury "ママから。もうお風呂に入り終わったの？なんて早いの？" 2
Azumi "あなたの番だよ。さあ急いで！" setFace(Fury,1_anxious) 1
Fury "15分あったはずなのに、残り5分。だめだ…" 2
narrator "彼女たちは準備をして、他の友達と集合します。" exit(Fury;Azumi) 1
Load(chap5)