showScene(true,topDown) next
setFace(Azumi,3_angry) next
Azumi "その場で四つん這いになって、頭と首を両手で覆って！急いでここから抜け出そう！" 1
Fury "私たちは今3階にいるから、1階は遠すぎるよ。すぐにテーブルの下に避難したほうがいいよ！" 2
Azumi "急げ！" exit(Fury;Azumi) 1
narrator "その後まもなく、地震は収まります。 They go down and out of the inn. After the situation is safe, they go back to the room." 2
enter(Fury) flip(Fury) setFace(Fury,1_anxious) setPosition(Fury,0.2) enter(Azumi) flip(Azumi) setFace(Azumi,3_anxious) setPosition(Azumi,0.5) next
Azumi "Well, it was frightening, wasn't it? Thankfully the table is sturdy so it can protect us from falling objects. But, why don't we just go outside to the open space when the earthquake happened?" 1
Fury "Because we are on the second floor, I am afraid that we will be hit by something falling down. If we are on the ground floor and close to the exit, then we can go outside and look for open space." 2
Load(chap4b2cont2)