1 playMusic(happytune)
enter(Fury) setPosition(Fury,0.5) setFace(Fury,1_happy) transBackground(01_kamartidur,radialClock) next
Fury "こんにちは、私の名前はフューリーです。私は一人っ子です。現在、日本からのお客さんが滞在しています。彼女の名前はあずみです。私にとって、彼女は妹のような存在です。" setFace(Fury,1_flat) move(Fury,0.8) id 2
enter(Azumi) flip(Azumi) setPosition(Azumi,0.5) setFace(Azumi,3_happy) multiplay next
Azumi "こんにちは、あずみです。私は現在インドネシアでの交換留学プログラムに参加しています。私とフューリーはたった1歳しか離れていません。この交換留学の間、私はフューリーの学校で学びました。今、私はフューリーの部屋で一緒に過ごしています。" setFace(Fury,1_happy) chat 1
Fury "ああ、そのとおり。サマーキャンププログラムに登録するための書類の締め切りが今夜だから、私には夜遅くまでつきあってくれる友だちが必要だよ。" 2
Azumi "頑張って、フューリー！合格したら、私に食事をおごってね。" 1
Fury "Ay ay, Capt! [setFace(Fury,1_anxious)] By the way, Azumi, have you heard the issue that there will be a major disaster in Indonesia at the end of this year?" 2
Azumi "Yes, I've heard of it. Natural disaster issue, right? The issue was discussed by my friends in class." 1
Fury "Yes, major disaster caused by natural event. What do you think if the disaster really happened?" 2
Azumi "The issue is uncertain. I think, don't worry too much." 1
Fury "ここが安全かどうか不安に思う？" 2
Azumi "フューリー、それは災害に対する備えがあるかどうかにかかっているよ。日本も、しょっちゅう災害があるよ。" 1
Fury "じゃあ、準備はいい？" 2
Azumi "Quite ready. Indeed, according to the news you heard, what disaster will occur?" 1
Fury "Earthquake. If an earthquake occurs near the coast, it might be followed by a tsunami." 2
Azumi "The time when an earthquake will occur cannot be predicted. Apart from earthquakes, tsunamis may also occur if landslides occur on the seabed or objects fall into the sea." 1
Fury "Yes, you are right. If a volcano erupts in the sea, it can also cause a tsunami. What should we prepare so that we are safe?" 2c
choice "What must be prepared to be able to get out of the house safely?"
{
  "棚をしっかり固定しよう。"
    score(jijoB) Load(chap0a)
  "玄関までの通路に何も家具をおかないこと。"
    score(jijoB) Load(chap0b)
  "近所の人たちと防災訓練を主催する。"
    score(kyojoB) Load(chap0c)
  "家具が倒れる危険性について教える。"
    score(kyojoB) Load(chap0d)
  "住宅の耐震基準を向上させる。"
    score(kojoB) Load(chap0e)
}