showScene(true,topDown) multiplay next
Fury "We must be ready." 2
Azumi "In Indonesia, is there any sign if an earthquake or tsunami happens?" 1
Fury "From the news, sound of bells, or maybe drum." 2
Azumi "Oh yeah, nowadays technology has developed, we can know it by the sound of sirens or notifications. What do you think should be prepared so we can get out of the house safely?" 1c
choice "What must Fury prepare so she can leave the house safely during earthquake?"
{
  "近所の人たちと防災訓練を主催する。"
    score(kyojoA) Load(chap1c)
  "家具が倒れる危険性について教える。"
    score(kyojoA) Load(chap1d)
  "棚をしっかり固定しよう。"
    score(jijoA) Load(chap1a)
  "玄関までの通路に何も家具をおかないこと。"
    score(jijoA) Load(chap1b)
  "住宅の耐震基準を向上させる。"
    score(kojoA) Load(chap1e)
}